[{"answer": "What I found, Piers, is something amazing, that local people -- lawyers, businessmen and others -- have set up what amounts to an ad hoc government with committees dealing everything, food supply, public health, even garbage collection.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "What have you found since getting there?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's not clear but it's a much more complicated situation.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Could this be over quickly?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I am well.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "A little.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Does it feel weird being on that side of the desk?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Do you like it?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Difficult.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "What did you make of him?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "I think he may not last.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What's your overview of him?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Which is extraordinary, right?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I don't think he's going to run.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "You think he's the kind of character that would?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Not really, no, because I'm going to do other things.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Do you feel more able to give opinion now out of the nightly show?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I would say he had a difficult start.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "If I asked you what you thought of Obama and how he's getting on, what would you say?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "They would win.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "What do you think would happen if they do?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, it's actually interesting.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Where did he finish?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "ING: But he -- I love Donald, but he does this every election.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "I mean Trump does have kind of appeal, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "CNN poll -- I think Kennedy won.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Who did?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Clinton.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Who would be the one in your lifetime that you think was the most effective president?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I'm dangerous.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Have you read the full quote?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, look --", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "I thought you are -- what you did was or what they did -- were you being facetious when you said I was dangerous?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Let me ask you.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Was that an attempt at British humor?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "About -- now about eight.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "How many of my shows have you watched?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "I haven't seen you dangerous yet.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "You have?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I suppose I've always oversold myself.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "That's not strictly true.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "I think -- I was only kidding.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "When you said dangerous, what did you mean?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Yes, it is British.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "British humor?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I miss asking questions.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What are the things that when you wake up you think, wow?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "No, twice.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Two things ticked me about that.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "For screaming at the officials?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Do you ever hit?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Have you got that in you?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I think television changed.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Why do you think the ratings fell in the way that they did in your last couple of years?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "You know it's like the old joke about enough about me, let's talk about you, what do you think of me?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "I thought -- you've always got to quit leaving the public wanting more, isn't it?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "It was tough.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "You shed a tear?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Wait a minute.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "You bet your ass they are.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "These are diamonds?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Richard.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Where did you get that ring?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Seven times.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Or is it seven times?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Never thought of it.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Did you ever think it might have been easy if the two of you just got together early?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "In a good way?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I like romance.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What do you -- I mean are you an incurable romantic at heart?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Until the flower guy said, you know, she leaves a note, just leave it.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "For how long?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Is this the last time?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Yes, tell me what you're up to.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "I'm going to -- we're going to have some announcements coming?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "It starts in April in Torrington, Connecticut, and I'm going to do comedy and talk about life.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "And when is your stand-up tour starting?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Well, this is a little gift for you.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Suspenders are for lady's underwear.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Do they call them braces?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "That's what the Brits think.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "So I've been wearing lady's underwear?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Dave was a brilliant man.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Let me ask you both -- and maybe start with you Alicia, why do you believe that it was the damage to Dave's head that caused what happened to him?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say -- I don't know if -- I don't want to put word's in Dave's mouth, if that's the real reason he took his life.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "So, clearly, when he wrote that, he believed that the -- what he had suffered since giving up football had made him reach the point of wanting to take his life?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Sometimes he would come home and he had extreme headaches, dizziness, and he was just tired and he would want to just lay down for a while and just relax.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Do you remember when he came home after those games, what kind of condition he was in?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "I did, playing in high school.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "You suffered a concussion yourself, didn't you?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "I think these guys that are playing in the NFL now are very large and very fast.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Do you think it's a credible link between that kind of impact damage and the depression and brain damage that follows afterwards?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "He was a great man.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Let me ask you, Tregg, what kind of man was your father?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "I would say that I'm very proud of Dave, that even in his darkest moment that he thought of others, and he wanted to help future athletes, future players that would come into the sport.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Alicia, what would you say about Dave now?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Amazingly, piers, the research is still pretty early.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "I make what he says is very correct.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "What do you make of what you heard from Sanjay?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I would want my father to do what he loved.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Tregg, let me ask you, finally, when you think of your father, does any part of you now wish he had never played NFL?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "I asked Tregg and Odis, who was a player with David, that same question yesterday.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "It's not going to get any better, is it?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "It was much tougher on Lindsay than it was on us.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "What are you feeling now?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "Justifiably, no doubt, 100 percent.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "It's been a wake up call for me.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 789, "question": "Will that be a wake up call for all of you, do you think?", "qSentId": 788}, {"answer": "She's afraid she is.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "Does Lindsay know she's going to jail?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "OHAN: No.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 805, "question": "Her lawyer said to you this is pretty likely?", "qSentId": 804}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 828, "question": "Do you think she's innocent of stealing the jewelry?", "qSentId": 827}, {"answer": "Of course she is.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 834, "question": "Is she scared, Michael?", "qSentId": 833}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "Do you think she could cope with being in jail, given the state that she's reached?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "People ask me that because they compare me to Billy Ray Cyrus, what he's going through.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 848, "question": "Do you think becoming famous and wealthy just made the whole situation ten times worse?", "qSentId": 847}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110223pmt", "aSentId": 875, "question": "Will you come back again and talk more about this?", "qSentId": 874}]